export const questions = [
	{
		"id": "1",
		"question": "Which of the following research methods is commonly used to estimate the heritability of a",
		"options": [
			"Adoption Studies",
			"Correlational Studies",
			"Case Studies",
			"Experimental Studies"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "2",
		"question": "Which of the following is a negative symptom of schizophrenia?",
		"options": [
			"Hallucinations",
			"Delusions",
			"Disorganized speech",
			"Avolition"
		],
		"answer": 4,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "3",
		"question": "Which theoretical perspective in personality psychology emphasizes the role of unconscious conflicts, early childhood experiences, and the influence of the id, ego, and superego?",
		"options": [
			"Humanistic perspective",
			"Trait perspective",
			"Psychodynamic perspective",
			"Social-cognitive perspective"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "4",
		"question": "According to Albert Bandura's social-cognitive theory, which of the following factors is crucial in the development of personality?",
		"options": [
			"Genetic predispositions",
			"Unconscious conflicts",
			"Observational learning and modeling",
			"Trait inheritance from parents"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "5",
		"question": "Unconditional positive regard is associated with",
		"options": [
			"Wolpe's systematic desensitization therapy",
			"Ellis's rational-emotive therapy",
			"Beck's cognitive therapy",
			"Rogers' client-centered therapy"
		],
		"answer": 4,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "6",
		"question": "According to the Five-Factor Model of personality, which of the following traits is associated with a high level of imagination, curiosity, and openness to new experiences",
		"options": [
			"Neuroticism",
			"Extraversion",
			"Openness",
			"Agreeableness"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "7",
		"question": "Jason is so preoccupied with staying clean that he showers as many times as 10 times each day. Jason would be diagnosed as suffering from what?",
		"options": [
			"ADHD",
			"OCD",
			"Schizophrenia",
			"Phobia"
		],
		"answer": 2,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "8",
		"question": "Which stage of Erik Erikson's psychosocial development theory occurs during infancy?",
		"options": [
			"Identity vs. Role Confusion",
			"Intimacy vs. Isolation",
			"Trust vs. Mistrust",
			"Autonomy vs. Shame and Doubt"
		],
		"answer": 3,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "9",
		"question": "According to Lawrence Kohlberg, at which stage of moral development do individuals make decisions based on self-interest and personal gain?",
		"options": [
			"Preconventional level",
			"Conventional level",
			"Postconventional level",
			"Principled level"
		],
		"answer": 1,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "10",
		"question": "Which of the following best defines the term \"development\" in the context of lifespan psychology?",
		"options": [
			"The process of aging & physical maturation",
			"The growth & changes that occur throughout a person's life",
			"The development of cognitive abilities only",
			"The process of reaching adulthood"
		],
		"answer": 2,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	// 
	/* {
		"id": "11",
		"question": "Which of the following is NOT a major milestone of cognitive development in Piaget's theory?",
		"options": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		],
		"answer": 0,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "12",
		"question": "A psychotic person would probably score the highest on which MMPI-2 scale?",
		"options": [
			"Depression",
			"Hysteria",
			"Schizophrenia",
			"Mania"
		],
		"answer": 0,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "13",
		"question": "Limbic system, Basal ganglia and Corpus striatum are pasts of which section of the brain?",
		"options": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		],
		"answer": 0,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": "14",
		"question": "",
		"options": [
			"",
			"",
			"",
			""
		],
		"answer": 0,
		"tags": [
			"psychology"
		]
	} */
]